不 不 安静
No, no. Just be quiet.
该死
Shit.
该死 该死 该死
Shit. Shit. Shit.
你他妈给我回来！
Get the fuck back here!
嘿，把那个该死的相机给我！
Hey, give me that fucking camera!
是的，你在看我发给你的视频？
Yeah, so you're watching that footage I sent?
是的，我在找，儿子，而你…
Yeah, I'm looking, son, and you...
也许你已经猜到了，是你的妻子雇我去干的
so as you probably guessed, your wife hired me to get that.
问题是如果我把这个给她看，她会不付我钱
The problem is if I show it to her, she stops paying me.
所以我在想你也许想还个价
So I was thinking you might want to make a counter-offer there.
哦，不管你想出多少价钱
Oh, and whatever number you come up with,
你最少要给我300块作为损坏我车的赔偿
you can put 300 bucks on top for the dent you put in my car.
好吧，反正是你刮掉的油漆
Well, you scratched the paint anyway.
你听好了，如果我明天没收到你的信息
You know what, if I don't hear from you by tomorrow,
你老婆就会得到那份文件 再见
your wife gets that file. Good-bye.
那么 现在的协议是什么？
So what's the deal now?
啊，也许一无所获 只是这个女人
Ah, probably nothing. Just this woman thinks
认为他的儿子失踪了
her son is missing.
他一个星期没去上课了
He hasn't been to class in a week.
他也不接她的电话
He won't answer her calls.
他很可能昏倒在一堆啤酒罐中
He's probably passed out in a pile of beer cans.
在这种情况下 我们要带孩子开车旅行
In which case we're gonna take the kid on a road trip
来获得一些费用，因为我们
and rack up some expenses, 'cause we're getting
处理这件事情期间每天能获得1000块
1,000 bucks a day on this one.
在这里左转
Turn left up here.
你的纽扣相机在工作么？
Your button cam's working?
是的，它在工作
Yeah, it's working.
是这里么？
This is it?
是的
Yeah.
这里看上去不像是谁的家
It doesn't look like anyone's home.
她没给你一把钥匙么？
She couldn't give you a key?
她没有她说了
She doesn't have one. She said the lock
后窗户的锁是坏的
on the back window's busted,
也许我们能从那儿进去
so maybe we can get in that way.
那警察还没来过这里么？
And the cops haven't been here?
没有，警灿谠于这些大学生失踪几天的事情
No, the cops don't give a shit about some college kid
一点也不在乎
who's missing for a couple days.
这里
Here.
那里面有人么？
Is there someone in there?
过来，快点，给我相机
Here. Come on, give me the cam.
里面什么也没有
There's nothing there.
我确定那里有该死的声音 听起来像是有人在里面
It sure as fuck sounded like there's something there.
这是一栋老房子
It's an old house.
而且，如果有人在里面
Besides, if there is somebody in there,
我倒想和他们谈谈
I'm gonna want to talk to 'em.
接着
Here.
你没事吧？
You all right?
还好
Just great.
你还好么？
You okay?
怎么了？
What?
你知道么？呆在这里，好么？
You know what? Stay in here, okay?
我要去检查一下这间公寓的其他地方
I'm gonna go check the rest of this apartment
确定一下这里没有其他人，好么？
and make sure no one else is in here, okay?
你带你的枪了么?是的
You got your gun? Yeah.
好的，很好只要… 只要，额
All right, good. Just... just, um,
把任何相关的东西都拖到车上好么？
pull anything relevant onto that drive. Okay?
并且全部记录
And record everything.
这是协议的一部分她希望我这么做
That was part of the deal. She likes me to do that.
好吧，你拿着我的照相机呢.
Well, you took my camera.
哦.那么…
Oh. Then...
好吧，我很快会回来
All right, so I'll be right back.
只是，额… 只是，我不知道
Just, um... just, I don't know,
看看那台电脑上有什么，好么？
see what's on that computer, okay?
如果那是加密的，我们就把它带回家
If it's encrypted, we can take it home.
如果不是，那就尽你可能的复制资料
If not, just pull what you can.
知道了
Got it.
露出她的乳头！
Show her tits!
我找到了一个新的
I found a new one.
从质量上来看是第二或者第四代
It's third or fourth generation from the quality.
我从一些家伙那里得到的 他们从小亚美尼亚
I got it from some guy down in little Armenia
的一个当铺下载的
with a pawn shop.
他绝不是你通常看到的那种
He is definitely not the type of guy you usually see
和我们交易的人，但我认为他是
on here trading with us, but I think he's somebody
值得再次探查的
who's worth checking in on again.
好吧这真实太奇怪了
Okay. That's fucking weird.
他的大部分收藏品，我想说
Most of his collection, I would say,
是鼻烟和卡值，但是他至少
was snuff and cp, but he had at least one
有一样东西是真实的
that was the real thing.
我甚至不觉得他知道那是什么
I don't even think he knew what it was.
总之…
Anyway...
一点点的发红，有些刺激物
A little bit of redness, some irritation,
但是它看上去还好  感觉如何？
but it looks okay. How's it working?
很好是的，我能看到
It's good. Yeah, I can see,
但是我的另一只眼睛如何？
but what about my other eye?
- 跟着我的手看  - 好的
- Follow.            - Okay.
你从眼中看不到任何东西？
You can't see anything out of your biological eye?
看不到
No.
好吧那现在呢？
Okay. How about now?
是的，我是说，稍微好一点儿了
Yeah. I mean, it's a little better.
只是有些模糊和朦胧
It's just kind of blurry and shadowy.
是的 好的
Yeah. All right.
好吧，因为你的假眼球是直接连到
Well, because your prosthesis is attached directly
你的视觉皮层的
to your visual cortex,
你的的真眼睛 本质上与你的相机眼睛相斗争
you real eye's essentially battling with your camera eye
来向你传送实时的景象
to give you input right now.
因此当你的大脑开始习惯有那个芯片时
So when your brain gets used to having that chip in there,
你要开始试着越来越
you should start to see more and more
不用你未受伤的眼睛来看东西
out of your uninjured eye again.
到那时，你可能会看到一些假信号
Until then, you might see some glitches.
你说的假信号是什么意思？
What do you mean by glitches?
额，这个现在还处在测试中
Well, this is just being tested now.
像你这样的眼部伤害是很罕见的
Eye injuries like yours are quite rare.
所以这就是为什么我们安装了一个录音芯片
So that's why we've installed a recording chip
植入了眼睛里 那样我们就可以测试接收到的数据
into the eye itself so we can test the data it's receiving.
是这样是的，关于那个
Right. Yeah, about that.
- 怎么了？  - 哦，我的上帝
- Yes?            - Oh, my God.
那么如果我想要私人空间，我该怎么做？
So if I want private time, what do I do?
我怎么关闭它？好吧，你不能
How do I turn this off? Well, you can't.
但是 这只是对于试用期
But that's just for this trial period.
你不能指望KPG公司
You can't expect the KPG corporation to just
只给你植入这个而不期望测试它的数据
give you this implant and not expect to test its data.
当然不能
Of course not.
所以你们准备围坐在那里，看我拉屎么？
So you guys are gonna sit around and watch me take shits?
我想说这是一个公平的让步 米德尔顿先生
I'd say that's a fair compromise, Mr. Middleton.
你可以在那期间看一份报纸，或者其他的
You can read a newspaper during, or something.
那么预约下周
So make an appointment for next week.
我们将看看它运转如何
We'll see how it's working.
如果你有任何问题打电话给我
Call me if you have any concerns.
好的谢谢你
All right. Thank you.
这到底怎么回事？
What the hell?
好的，先生 好吧
All right, man. All right.
你确定你没事儿，伙计？
You sure you gonna be okay, bud?
是的，伙计 我没事 我很好
Yeah, dude, I'm good. I'm good.
如果你有什么需要的就给我留言
Give me a shout if you need anything.
回头见
See ya.
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
我把那个控制器放哪儿了？
Where'd I put that controller?
好吧，然后
All righty, then.
怎么…
What the...
好吧
okay.
这他妈什么情况？有人么？
What the fuck? Hello?
有人么？哦，拜托
Hello? Oh, come on.
这他妈是什么？
What the fuck is this shit?
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
上帝啊！该死！
Jesus! Fuck!
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
是的 是的 我能分辨出
Yeah. Yeah, I can tell the difference
一束光和一个该死的血腥人的区别，好么？
between a burst of light and a fucking bloody person, okay?
我不知道，你告诉我 你是医生
I don't know, you tell me. You're the doctor.
听着，我明天去你那儿，你要帮我
Look, I'm coming in there tomorrow, and you're gonna fix
修理这个该死的东西，还有刚才那个东西，好么？
this fucking thing, and that's that, okay?
好吧 好的，谢谢你
Fine. All right, thank you.
听到么？
Hello?
有人在下面么？
Is somebody down there?
认真点，别惹我
Seriously, don't fuck with me.
哦，上帝该死
Oh, God damn it.
有人么？
Hello?
该死！
Shit!
哦，妈的
Oh, fuck.
这他妈是什么？
What the fuck?
有人么？
Hello?
该死！嗯，好吧！
Shit! Uh, okay!
我很好 谢谢你，你可以走
I'm good. Thank you, you can go.
哦，该死！
Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck!
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God.
该死的
God damn it.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
嘿，你在那里么？
Hey, are you in there?
听着，我能通过窥视孔看到你
Look, I can see you through the peephole.
你昨天不是在医生的办公室么？
Weren't you at the doctor's office yesterday?
是的
Yeah.
好的，那么交易什么？你在跟踪我？
Okay, so what's the deal? Are you following me?
我没跟踪你，听着，只要打开门
I'm not following you. Look, just open the door.
好的，听着，我无意冒犯
All right, listen, I don't mean to be rude,
可是这事很奇怪，你知道么？
but it's kind of weird, you know?
你看，你看到了奇怪的东西？
Look, are you seeing weird stuff?
看上去像是个死人的家伙？
Like people who look dead?
你真的应该打开门
You should really open the door.
谢谢你 我叫克拉丽莎
Thank you. I'm Clarissa.
是的，进来吧
Yeah, come on in.
- 这地方很不错，先生  - 谢谢
- Nice place, man.     - Thanks.
你有啤酒么？
Do you have any beer?
我有 是的
I do. Yes.
止痛片如何？医生给你了一些没？
What about painkillers? Did the doctor give you any?
没有，其实我没有任何疼痛
No, I'm not actually in any pain.
我只要喝杯啤酒
I'll just take a beer then.
听着，克拉丽莎，我真的准备离开这里
Look, Clarissa, I'm actually on my way out of here.
伙计，如果你不听完我要说的
Dude, you're not gonna get anywhere
那你哪儿也别想去
if you don't hear what I have to say.
只是给我来杯啤酒，给你自己也来一杯
Just give me a beer, get one for yourself.
你会需要它的
You're gonna need it.
好吧
Right.
- 谢谢  - 当然
- Thanks. - Sure.
我出身就是聋子
I was born deaf.
当我16岁是，我的父母带我去
When I was 16, my parents put me up
植入了一个新的人工耳蜗
for a new cochlear implant.
显然，它很奏效
It worked, obviously.
但是是我开始能够分辨出
But I began to be able to pick up
我环境中的某些频率
certain frequencies in my environments.
你的眼睛出什么事儿的？
What happened to your eye anyway?
我以前，额… 再一次车祸中
I was in a, um... in a car accident.
那么那个小女孩是谁？
So who's the little girl?
什么小女孩？
What little girl?
这里有个小女孩
There's a little girl here.
我进来的时候听到了她的哭声
I heard her crying when I came in.
但是你知道…
But you know...
我现在听不到她了
I don't hear her now.
有些人永远也听不到或者看到他们
Some people never hear them or see them.
也许在他们一生中会有一次
Maybe once in their entire lives,
如果他们打开它
if they're open to it.
所以当你可以感觉到他们时，他们知道
So when you can sense them, they know.
他们可以交流
They can tell.
这就是为什么我想找到你来提醒你
That's why I wanted to find you. To warn you.
提醒我什么？
Warn me about what?
是的
Yeah.
你与他们的互动越多
The more you interact with them,
他们就越能触碰你
the more they can touch you,
伤害你
hurt you, stuff.
好吧，明天我要把这个该死的东西
Well, tomorrow I'm gonna get this fuckin' thing
从我的头里弄出来，那样就行了，对么？
taken out of my head, and that'll be that, right?
别那么肯定
Don't be so sure.
你以前有伤害过某人么？
Have you ever done anything bad to anybody?
听着，如果你把植入的芯片取出来
Look, if you get the implant taken out,
他们仍然会在那里
they're still gonna be there.
你只是不能看到他们
You're just not gonna be able to see them.
我不知道，也许那样会好些
I don't know, maybe that's better.
好吧，我猜哦，该死！
Well, I guess. Oh, shit!
嗯，我现在不想吓你
Um, I don't want to alarm you right now,
但是有一个该死的恐怖的家伙正站在你背后
but there's a fucking creepy dude standing right behind you.
我知道我能听见他
I know. I can hear him.
- 你认识他或者其他的？  - 他是我的叔叔
- Do you know him or something? - He was my Uncle.
哦，当然，是的我的意思是…
Oh, of course, right. I mean...
好吧，我不是故意叫他恐怖的家伙，但是我的意思是…
well, I didn't mean to call him creepy, but I mean...
他是一个好人
he wasn't a nice person.
好吧…
Okay...
听着，我知道怎么让他离开
Listen, I know how to make him go away.
只要盯着我看好吧
Just focus on me. Okay.
哦！
Oh!
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
别，别看他，看我
No, don't look at him, look at me.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
好吧，你个混蛋科学家
All right, you scientist assholes,
我要那个画面的副本
I want a copy of that footage.
同样的，我要你把它刻入一个碟里或者诸如此类的东西
Like, I want you to put it on a disc or something,
但是是别看它
but don't watch it.
只要把它给我，好么？
Just get it to me, okay?
好的
All right.
哦，该死
Oh, fuck.
哦，该死的
Oh, God damn it.
克拉丽莎… 是你么？
Clarissa... Is that you?
嘿
Hey.
哦，该死！
Oh, shit!
嘿
Hey.
哦，上帝
Oh, God.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
这他妈是什么？
What the fuck?
克拉丽莎，把你的手给我！
Clarissa, give me your hand!
妈的
Fuck.
我抓住你了 我抓住你了
I got you. I got you.
哦，该死！
Oh, fuck!
哦… 哦… 哦…
Oh...Oh...Oh...Oh...
好的
All right.
你要离开这里，你个傻瓜
You're coming out of here, you fucker.
额… 哦，我不能看这个该死的
Eww...Oh, I can't look at this shit.
哦，上帝
Oh, God.
好吧
Okay.
哦，该死！
Oh, shit!
拉里拉里
Larry. Larry!
嘿，声音小点儿 什么？
Hey, keep your voice down. What?
怎么了？没什么
What's wrong? Nothing.
我刚才看到了一些很奇怪的东西
I just watched something really weird.
那不是真的，所以…
It couldn't have been real, so...
好吧 那台电脑上有什么东西么？
okay. Is there anything on that computer?
我在复制他的硬盘
I'm cloning his hard drive now.
应该不会太久
It shouldn't take too long.
这里，看这个
Here, look at this.
磁带是我最后的链接
Tape is the final link for me.
我知道  你已经发布了一大部分
I know a lot of you have posted that it only affects you
如果你按照正确的顺序播放 那它只会影响你…
if you play it in a correct sequence.
但是 我一直在实验
But I've been experimenting on...
是这个孩子么？
Is this the kid?
是的，是他
Yeah, that's him.
我在他的房间里找到一些笔记
I found some notebooks in his room.
像是日记 虽然大部分只是胡说
Kind of like journals. Mostly just nonsense, though.
我现在要扔了它们
I'm going through them right now.
你为什么不，例如，继续看这个带子？
Why don't you, like, keep looking at these tapes?
孩子是一个收藏家 我不知道谁知道呢？
Kid's a collector. I don't know. Who knows?
也许有些东西和他们相关
Maybe there's something relevant on them.
哦额… 好吧
Oh. Um... Okay.
我们都只用电磁能量
We're all just electromagnetic energy,
然后这些模拟磁带
then these analog tapes capturing images
捕捉超自然影像
of the supernatural,
他们会影像我们的大脑皮层
they can affect our cerebral cortex.
他们… 他们…
They... they...
嘿，室贝
Hey, babe.
别对我说“嘿，室贝”麦克沙利文
Don't "hey, babe" me, Mike Sullivan.
我门准备去吃早餐
We're supposed to be having breakfast.
是的，但这是一个美好的一天
Yeah, but it's a beautiful day.
我只想骑自行车出去兜兜风
I just want to take the bike out for a spin.
我想让你带我去兜风
I wanted you to take me for a spin.
你知道，你骑那辆车比我起得好多了
You know, you ride that bike more than you ride me.
是的，但是你知道，自行车只是一个物质的东西，宝贝
Yeah, but you know the bike is just a physical thing, babe.
嗯   嗯
Mm-hmm.
现在，跟我说你爱我！
Now, tell me you love me.
我爱你
I love you.
好的，好极了  注意安全，宝贝
Okay, good enough. Be safe, babe.
好的，再见
All right, bye.
请帮帮我！
Help me! Please!
- 你还好吗？  - 我的男朋友！
- Are you okay? - My boyfriend!
你得帮帮我男朋友！
You have to help my boyfriend!
啊  我正准备帮
I'm getting help.
不！求求你  帮帮他
No, please! Help Dan!
噢！天哪！
Oh, God!
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，到我这里来
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, stay with me.
狗屎！他妈的！
Shit! Fuck!
神啊
God.
谁在那儿？
Who's there?
警察就在我的后面   你最好赶紧跑
The police are right behind me, so you better run.
我有他妈的一根大棍子！
I got a big fucking stick!
什么鬼东西？
What the fuck?
嘿，嘿，赶快，我们得走了！
Hey, hey, come on, we got to go!
哇！啊！
Whoa!
啊！滚开！
Get off!
死吧，你这个臭婊子！你这个臭婊子！
Die, you fucking bitch! You fucking bitch!
救命！！救命！
Help. Help!
亲爱的，你确定知道要去哪里吗？
Honey, you sure you know where you're going?
这看起来不像是一条路
This does not look like a trail.
当然 我知道要去哪里
Of course I know where I'm going.
相信我 你怎么能这么说？
Trust me. How can you tell?
- 好的，这儿以前是一条路    - 这儿没路
- Well, it used to be a trail. - There's no trail here.
看起来你一点都不熟悉吧？
This doesn't look familiar to you at all?
不，不是的
No, not whatsoever.
我的意思是很漂亮，我会给你很多
I mean it's pretty, I'll give you that much.
哦，妈的
Holy shit.
噢，我的神
Oh, my God.
他是…
Is he...
我想是
I think so.
看上去他被什么东西咬了
It looks like he's been bit by something.
你可以摸摸他的脉搏，确定一下
Will you check his pulse, just to be sure?
没了
Nothing.
我的神啊！我的意思是，我们能做什么呢？
My God, I mean, what could have done this?
我不知道我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
- 一只动物？ - 是的，你好
- An animal?  - Yes, hello.
我们发现一个人他好像… 浑身是血
We found someone. He's, like, covered in blood,
没有脉搏了
and there's no pulse.
我们在自行车道上 然后…
We're on the bike trails and...
我的意思是，他看上去被什么东西咬了
I mean, it looks like he's been bit by something.
被咬了一口，是吗？这是我的猜测
It's a bite, right? That would be my guess.
这是国家公园还是什么的？我不记得了
What state park is this? I don't remember.
这是金石国家公园
This is gold stone state park.
是的，我们在金石国家公园
Yeah, we're at gold stone state park.
但是我不确定，我们确切在哪里
But I'm not sure, exactly, where we are here.
这是…从高速下来的路
It's the... the trail off of highway one.
是的，在高速下来的小路上
Yeah, on the trails off of highway one.
好吧，他们派人来了吗？
Okay. They're sending somebody?
他们要派…联系我们和公园护林员
They're gonna send... connect us with a park ranger.
好吧，哦，妈的
Okay. Holy shit.
神啊
God.
- 等等    - 亲爱的，你在干嘛？
- Wait a minute. - Honey, what are you doing?
- 我认为我听到一些声音  - 什么声音？
- I think I heard a noise. - What kind of noise?
我不知道 好像他在说什么
I don't know. It's like he said something.
嘿…嘿，嘿！
Hey...Hey. Hey!
放开我  放开我，伙计！
Get off me! Get off me, man!
放开他！停下！停下！
Get off of him! Stop it! Stop!
放开他！啊！
Get off him!
不！放开！
No! Get off!
不！停下！放开！
No! Stop it! Get off!
啊！哦，我的神啊！
Oh, my God!
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday!
生日快乐！比安卡
Happy Birthday, Bianca.
好吧，亲爱的
All right, honey.
走！走！
Go! Go!
上车上车！我们走
Get in the car. Get in the car. Let's go.
快，快，快开 快点，开快点
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Faster, faster.
快点，快点，快点，快点，快点
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry, hurry, hurry.
进去 上车吧！上车吧！
Get in. Get in! Get in!
快点，伙计 是的！
Come on, man. Yeah!
啊！不！不！
No! No!
哦！妈的！
Oh, shit!
喂？
Hello?
迈克？迈克，迈克，迈克
Mike? Mike, Mike, Mike.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你的屁股    拨打我，傻瓜
You butt-dialed me, goofball.
哦，好吧，我爱你，宝贝
Oh, well, I love you, baby.
不能等你回家，再见
Can't wait for you to get home. Bye.
这儿情况怎么样？
Hey, how's it going in here?
嘿
Hey.
抱歉，我肯定是睡着了
Sorry. I must've fallen asleep.
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你的鼻子流血了头抬起来
Your nose is bleeding. Don't tilt your head back.
它只是进了你的喉咙
It'll just go down your throat.
您偏头痛吗？嗯…
This one of your migraines? Mm...
嗯，你钱包里的是你的药吗？
Mmhmm. Are your pills in your purse?
是的
Yeah.
他们不在这儿
They're not in here.
你能让他们留在你的公寓吗？
Could you have left them at your apartment?
也行 我不知道 我…
Maybe. I don't know. I...
好吧，你想让我做些什么呢？
all right, so what do you want me to do?
我们来的路上有家药店
We passed a drugstore on the way here.
需要我回去帮你买点阿司匹林或者别的药吗
I could go back, get you some aspirin or something.
好吧，我不想动
Yeah. I don't feel like moving.
不过把你一个人丢在这儿我不太安心
All right, well, I feel kind of weird leaving you...
你快去吧
just go.
好的，那我马上回来
Okay. I'll be right back.
马利克，我这儿有声音但是没有图像
Malik, I'm getting audio, but no visual.
检查一下是不是连接问题稍等
Check the connection. Wait, wait, wait.
现在怎么样？
Okay, how 'bout now?
嗯，好了
现在怎么样？
That's... okay, we're good.
- 好了吗？   - 好了
- We're good? - We're good.
给我看看
All right. Let me see.
干得不错，现在切换到莉娜那边
All right, perfect. Now switch to Lena-cam.
好的
All right.
能看见我吗
Do you see me, gents?
很清楚，亚当
Crystal clear. Adam?
你那儿怎么样？
Can you tell?
不行这边什么都看不见
No. From here, not a thing.
但是，如果我放大一些…
But if I zoom in...
你在看她最上面的扣子，是吗，亚当？
The top button, Adam. Well?
好吧，我们姑且相信你有正当理由 一定要找到那颗扣子
Let's just say you really have to be looking for it.
亚当
Yo, Adam.
把间谍相机递给我    在哪儿？
Would you pass me the spy cam? Where?
在我包里，前面一点
In my bag. In the front.
- 好的  - 谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks, man.
接住了
Here, heads up.
你知道吗，你就是个混蛋
You're a fucking dick, you know that?
好吗，伙计们？
Okay, guys?
嗨，莉蒂亚
Hi, Lydia. Oh...
嗯，好了
Yeah, all right.
噢，等会儿，等会儿
Oh, wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
等会儿
Wait.
嗨，莉娜，你想要一个升级版的项链吗？
Hey, Lena, you want to upsize that thing?
不，这个东西太奇怪了，我根本不想戴它
No, this is creepy, man. I don't want to wear this.
嗨，杰尼，这个归你了
Hey, Joni, this belongs to you, man.
杰尼，亚当，过来
Joni, Adam, come here.
来了来了
Coming, coming, coming.
杰尼，灯光不要太亮
Joni, not too bright.
亚当
Adam.
瞧，还有其他人在这拍摄呢，伙计们
Hey, we're not the only one filming, guys.
是啊
Yeah.
好了
Okay.
哥们儿，能快一点不？
Dude, can you speed things up?
- 别忘了这个，快去  - 好
- Don't forget his. Go. - Cool.
哥们儿，这个麦克风上有血迹
Dude, there's blood on the mic.
你还好吧？
You okay?
莉娜，你还好吗？
Lena, you okay?
别管我，你们开始吧
Just start without me.
- 你确定？  - 嗯
- You sure? - Yeah.
好的，那么
Yeah, um...
不好意思 打断一下
Hey, you know what? Sorry.
需要我过去看看莉娜吗
You want me to go check on Lena?
看看她好点没
Just to make sure she's fine.
嗨，前娜，你好些了吗？
Hey, Lena. You okay?
莉娜，怎么了？
Lena, what's wrong?
莉娜，发生了什么事？
Yo. Hey, Lena. What happened?
嗯，马利克？
Um...Malik?
- 真的吗？  - 是我不好
- Seriously? - My bad.
我以为我昨天充过电了
I thought I charged it yesterday.
没事儿，我来处理
Man... All right, I got this.
电池，电池
Batteries, batteries.
亚当，这情况不止一天了
It's been over a day, Adam.
听着，要知道
Listen, I need to know whether
不管是我还是你告诉马利克这件事
it's going to be me or you telling Malik.
我们都对不起他
We owe it to him.
你确定孩子是我的？
Are you even sure it's mine?
- 马利克和我没…  - 没什么？
- Malik and I haven't... - haven't what?
已经有一段时间了
It's been a while.
该死的 他可是我的…
Fuck! He's my fucking...
他妈的 他还是我最好的朋友呢
he's my fucking best friend.
而且他是我的未婚夫
And he's my fiance.
亚当，我怀孕了…
Adam, I am pregnant...
你是孩子的爸爸
And you're the father.
该死的 遮住你的摄像机
Just cover your fucking camera.
你以为我愿意这样吗？
Do you think I wanted this to happen?
快，快，听我说
Hey, hey, come on, come on. Listen.
我们可以去找一个人，做出弥补，没有人会受到伤害
We can go see someone, fix this, no one's hurt.
- 搞什么？  - 怎么了？
- What the fuck? - What? What?
滚你妈的  我根本不需要你！
Fuck you! I don't need you.
我要自己去跟马利克说
I'll tell Malik myself.
我留不留住这个孩子，他会不会离开我
And whether or not I keep this, and whether or not he walks,
都与你无关
I still don't fucking need you!
你说什么？
What?
你听见了
You heard me.
那好，就这么决定了
Fine. Decision made.
我们就是一群混蛋！！！
Fuck me, fuck you, fuck him.
老天，真该死！
God damn it.
哦，上帝！
Oh, shit! Jesus!
该死的！
What the fuck?
去他妈的！
Fuck it!
该死的！
What the fuck?
先生，那该死的是什么，先生…
Sir, what the fuck? Sir...
等等，等等，停，停
wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on.
停，快停 噢，不，这是怎么了？
Hold on, man. Oh, no. What?
喂，停下，停下！！
Hey! Stop! Stop!
噢，该死，该死！
Oh, fuck. Fuck!
阿门
Amen.
不，不，不！
No, no, no, no!
喂！
Hey!
该死的！
Fuck!
哦，天啊！
Holy shit!
- 我操！ - 帮帮我！
- Oh, fuck! - Help me!
妈的！
Shit!
亚当，快点跑，把她找到！
Adam, run. Go find her!
快点！
Go!
不好意思，兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
哇，这么…
Whoa. What...
恶心
the fuck.
哦，妈的
Oh, shit.
我操！
Fuck!
哦，妈的！
Oh, fuck!
- 莉娜！ - 亚当！
- Lena!     - Adam!
我操，这个贱人！
Fuck you, bitch!
他妈的
Fuck.
莉娜，镇定下来 我在这里，我陪着你
Lena, calm down. I'm here, I'm here.
来，给我手啊！啊！
Come on.
你他妈的快点把我带走！
Get it the fuck out of me!
把它从我身体里弄走！啊！
Get it...Out of me!
哦…
Oh...
哦，妈的
Oh, shit.
这是什么
What the...
乔尼！
Joni!
哦，我操！
Oh, fuck!
不！乔尼！
No! Joni!
哦，天啊！
Oh, Jesus!
他妈的给我滚开！
Get the fuck... go!
哦，我操！
Oh, fuck!
哦！
Oh!
哦，妈的！
Oh, shit!
我操
Fuck.
哦，他妈的
Oh, fuck.
快点！天啊，帮帮我！快点！
Come on! God, help me! Come on!
哦，妈的！
Oh, shit!
该死的！
Oh, fuck!
我操！他妈的！
Fuck! Fuck!
该死的！
Fuck!
我操
Fuck.
哦，我操！哦，天啊
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
快点，快点，快点，再快点！
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
爸爸
Papa.
嘿，宝贝，我给你带了一些阿士匹灵和布洛芬
Hey, baby, so I got you both aspirin and ibuprofen,
因为我认为…
because I figured...
哦，不
oh, no.
帮帮我！
Help!
有人能帮我吗！
Somebody help me!
你为什么要这么做？
Why did you do this?
来尝尝 我们屠杀的
Come taste the flesh
鲜肉，上帝的宠儿
of our slaughtered beast, earth creature.
是的，我们可以吃你身上的肉，收集你的皮肤当衣服
Yeah, so we can eat your body and collect your skin suit.
是的！你会掉进我们的陷阱里，白痴！
Aha! You fell for our trap, earth fool.
现在你会成为我们美味的佳肴
Now you will be our delicious murder.
快点，把它放进我的肚子里
Quick, put him in my digestive container
我可以给他喂维持生命的水
so I can feed off of his life juice.
这是什么？
What the fuck?
把狗放下，猪屎豆
Put that dog down, rattlebox.
你给它喂点生热狗，他快生病了
You keep feeding him raw hot dogs, he's gonna get sick.
我不想跟在它后面
I don't want to be the one pulling tapeworms
给它拉绦虫
our of our dog's behind.
哦，坦克，小跟屁虫
Oh, tank. Ass worms.
- 你们在拍视频吗？    - 是的
- Are you guys filming this? - Affirmative.
好 那么我们去制作带子 你们好好做家务
Good. Then we got it on tape you got your chores.
- 那乔妮干什么？  - 不
- What about Jenn?  - No.
她有考试 需要复习
She's got an exam to study for,
我希望你们不要打扰她
and I want you two to leave her alone.
20分钟内，若克就会过来了，知道吗？
You know in 20 minutes, Zack's gonna roll up in here, right?
小子们，照顾好坦克
Guys, look after tank.
知道吗？
Okay?
你的妈妈很爱你
Your mother loves you.
做得很好，坦克
Good job, tank.
好家伙
Good buddy.
- 很准时   - 乔妮在哪？
- Right on time. - Where's Jenn?
- 她在卧室学习    - 什么？我听不清你说的话！
- She's in her room studying. - What? I can't hear you.
她在她的卧室
She's in her fucking room.
录音机声音太大了，我听不清
I can't fuckin' hear over this radio.
什么？
What the hell?
- 你说她在她的卧室吗？  - 是的
- You say she was in her room? - Yeah.
哦，很好
Oh, perfect.
这是他妈的什么？加里
What the fuck, Gary?
为什么你们花了这么长时间？
What the hell took you guys so long?
我们玩篮球玩输了
We fuckin' lost our baseball game.
- 因为你们很羞劲  - 你才差劲
- 'Cause you guys suck. - You suck.
我们今天玩什么？
So what's up for today?
哦，是的
Oh, yeah.
我们有  些计划
We got some shit planned.
我姐姐和她的朋友们出去了 我们走吧
My sister and all her friends are out back. Let's go.
我们让雨下起来吧！
Let's make it rain!
- 你姐姐的朋友漂亮吗？  - 漂亮
- Your sister's friend hot? - Yes.
嘿，谁想喝爸爸的啤酒？
Hey, who wants some of daddy's beer?
你姐姐会疯的
Your sister's gonna be so pissed.
是的，她很可能会被气死
Yeah, she's probably gonna shit out her vag.
说定了
Gross.
嘿，兰迪，你准备还要让你姐姐湿身吗？
Hey, Randy, are you ready to get your sister wet?
他妈的，花花公子 不要拍我的鸡巴
Fuck off, dude. Don't film my dick.
准备 瞄准 开火！
Ready, aim, fire!
哦，我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
哦，我的天啊！成功了！
Oh, my God! Yeah!
- 他们湿透了！  - 真的！
- Get drenched! - Seriously!
滚开！你这卑鄙的家伙！
Get out of here! Go, you fucking twerps!
笨蛋！
Fuckers!
我会反击你们的，小贱人！
I'm gonna break your backs, you little shits!
接受我们的攻击吧，小男孩
Take my hot love, loverboy.
哦，我操！他妈的！
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
狗娘养的！停下！
Son of a bitches! Stop!
我操！啊！这很搞笑！
Fuck you!  Hilarious!
- 明天见啦    - 我会报复你们的！
- See you tomorrow. - Get the fuck back here!
他妈的快点把我弄出去！
Get me out of this fucking cage!
回见，小贱人
See you later, biatch.
回来，你这个贱人！
Come back here, you bitch!
妈的，你的姐姐很性感
Holy shit, your sister's hot.
滚开，你妈也很性感
Fuck off, so is your mom.
丹尼，你在干什么？
Danny, what are you doing?
他们真的在做爱吗？
Are they actually doing it?
是的？我敢打赌
They are, I bet you.
废话，他们在做爱
Holy crap, they are doing it.
我们毁了他们的约会吧
Let's ruin their fuckin' party.
好的，来吧！
All right, hit it.
滚出去，兰迪！
Get out, Randy!
生孩子！生孩子！
Babies making babies! Babies making babies!
哦，我操！滚出去，兰迪！滚留去！
Oh, fuck! Get out, Randy! Get out!
- 生孩子！   - 加里！
- Babies making babies! - Gary!
就是这样！
That is it!
我会把你的鸡巴锯下来！
I'm gonna fucking rip your dicks off!
把灯关掉！
Turn off the light!
- 走，走，走！ - 滚回来！
- Go, go, go! - Get back here!
哦，我的天啊，他就像在放屁一样
Oh, my God, that was so lame.
把灯关掉，把灯关掉
Turn off the light, turn off the light.
我会爆你菊花的
I tasted your piss,
现在我会尝尝你的血是什么味道的！
now I'm gonna taste your fucking blood!
你们看见那个了吗？
Do you guys see that?
他妈的那是什么？
What the fuck is that?
我不知道 感觉就像是重力一样…
I don't know. It kinda looks like a gravity...
给我那个照相机！
give me that fucking camera!
让他走吧，你这个贱人！
Let him the fuck go, you piece of shit!
你他妈的在玩我吗，兰迪？
Are you fucking kidding me, Randy?
你现在想打架吗？滚开，兰迪！
You want to fight right now? Fuck off, Randy!
你为什么这么让人讨厌？我没有T恤穿！
Why are you such an asshole? I didn't have a shirt on!
镇定下来，这不算是大事
Calm down, it's not even a big deal.
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
你现在应该学习，而不是他妈的鬼混
You were supposed to be studying, not slam hogging.
哦，关了它，加里，要不然我就把这个带子毁了
Oh, shut it, Gary, and if I can't fucking erase this film,
我他妈的会把它砸了的
I'm gonna fucking smash this camera.
你们这些滥同性恋
You're bunch of fucking faggots.
你可以吸我的小弟弟
You can suck my dick.
我不想！
I don't want to!
把它放下 放回去
Put it down. Put it back.
就是这样 我他妈的现在得到你了
This is it. I fucking got you now,
你这个贱人
you piece of shit.
在搞什么？你在看什么？
What the fuck? What is it?
他在干什么？哦，他妈的！
What's he doing? Oh, fuck!
他在说什么？什么？
He's fucking spankin' it. He's what?
- 他在自慰     - 哦，我的天啊
- He's stretching his dick. - Oh, my God.
- 他射精了   - 哦，天啊
- He's jerking off. - Oh, God.
- 就是这样   - 那很恶心
- This is it. - That's disgusting.
不 就是这样 詹尼 就是这样
No, this is it, Jenn. This is it.
这样我们就可以把他送回去了
This is how we get that fucker back.
坦克，就呆在这，他们现在在干吗？
Stay still, tank. Is this how they do it?
是  ，是  ，我认为…我认为这很正常
Yeah, yeah, I think... I think it's good.
等  会，在他射在睡袋之前
Just, we got to get in there
我们就进去
before he lubes up that sleeping bag.
很恶心
So disgusting.
来吧，这主意很好，我们快点
Come on, it's good. Let's just do this.
来吧，好吧
Come on. Okay.
帮我把他放下来
Help me get him down.
去看看兰迪
Go see Randy.
坦克，快点，出去
Tank, go, get out of here.
哦，我操！坦克，回来！
Oh, fuck! Tank, come back!
哇，兰迪 你手上的功夫挺好的呀！
Well, if it isn't Randy handy the fucking hand job.
抓住你的小弟弟，你个猥琐的男人
Caught you sticky-handed, you little come-dick.
- “来吧 小弟弟”  - 乔妮，你会毁了我的
- "Come-dick." - Jenn, you'll ruin my life.
求求你了，把相机给我吧 是的
Please give me the camera. Yeah, right.
我会把它放在网上的
I'm putting this all over the Internet.
- 发生什么事了？    - 哦 没事
- What's going on in here? - Oh, nothing.
我们只是看到你的朋友在自慰
We just caught your friend milking his dick in here.
你们进来的时候 我们已经睡着了吗？
You were coming while we were sleeping?
我操你们两个贱人！
Fuck you and fuck you!
- 妈的   - 这是怎么了？
- Holy shit. - What was that?
发生什么了？
What's going on?
有人在门口站着
There's someone at your door.
你爸爸的枪在哪放着？
Where does your dad keep his gun?
在密室里
In the closet.
哦，我的天啊 哦，天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
告诉我这是你的朋友
Please tell me this is you guys.
不，根本不是
No, it's fucking not.
是的，有人站在我家的门口
Yeah, there's some people in front of our house.
他们把电源掐断了
They just cut the power.
高速公路的103号，1967好的，请快一些
Highway 103, 1967. Okay, hurry.
不要到处转了！
Stop playing around!
在我蹦了你之前 把你的脸露出来！
Show your faces before I blow 'em off!
若克！
Zack!
若克！妈的！
Zack! Shit!
给我那个手电筒，加里 若克！
Give me that strobe light, Gary. Zack!
哦！ 天啊，哦，天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
我现在想回家
I think I want to go home.
- 你们听见了吗？  - 是的，我听见了
- Did you guys hear that? - Yeah, I do.
瞧你，你听见了吗？
Jenn, did you hear that?
听见什么？
Hear what?
加里！
Gary!
救命啊！救命啊！
Help! Help me!
詹妮，救命！ 救命！詹妮！救命！
Jenn, help! Help! Jenn, help!
救命啊！詹妮！救命！
Help, Jenn, help!
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
盖里  盖里
Gary! Gary!
- 你看见他了吗？  - 我什么都看不见
- Do you see him? - I can't see anything.
过来
Come here, tank.
嘿  孩子  哦  好孩子
Hey, boy. Oh, good boy.
兰迪 救我
Randy, help me.
我想我需要去医院
I think I need to go to the hospital.
听着 你很好 别去看它就好
Listen, you're fine. Just don't look at it.
- 好吧  - 过来  坦克
- Okay. - Come on, tank.
- 你要背着坦克  - 快点
- You need to carry tank. - Come on.
快点 小狗
Come on, dog!
盖里
Gary!
天哪  盖里！
Holt shit, Gary!
天哪  快来  快来
Holy shit! Come on. Come on, bud.
兰迪  帮我把他弄上码头
Randy, help me get him on the dock.
快来  帮帮我
Come on. Help me.
快点 快点 兰迪
Come on. Come on, Randy.
把他弄出来
Help him out.
抓到了吗？抬起他的腿
You got him? Lift his legs.
- 拉！  - 该死！
- Pull!  - Shit. Shit!
他还好吗
Is he okay?
不知道，  没有呼吸了
I don't know. He's not breathing.
- 妈的 - 妈的
- Shit. - Shit.
他没在呼吸了！
I don't think he's fucking breathing.
拜托 盖里 醒来  我该怎么做？
Come on, Gary, wake up. What do I do?
- 心脏复苏！  - 怎么做？怎么做？
- CPR! CPR!     - How? How? How? How?
抬起他的后脑勺，心脏按压
Tilt his head back and pump his chest.
拜托啊
Come on, bud.
- 人工呼吸      - 撑住 伙计
- Breathe in his mouth. - Come on, bud.
快点
Hurry up!
- 盖里 快点！  - 哦 糟糕！
- Come on, Gary! - Oh, shit!
快点 快点 快点 醒来啊
Hurry, hurry, hurry! Come on! Come on, bud!
- 给他人工呼吸  - 快醒来啊 盖里！
- Put your mouth on his mouth. - Come on, Gary!
耶稣！
Jesus Christ!
快点啊！盖里！
Come on, Gary!
快点！盖里!给我起来！
Come on, Gary! Get up!
快快
Go! Go!
跑啊！快  跑 快
Run! Go! Run! Go!
过来  孩子
Come here, boy!
坦克  快点，快点 快点
Tank, hurry! Hurry! Tank!
走 走 走 走 走 我在你后边
Go, go, go, go! Right behind you.
好了 坦克 过来 坦克 过来
Okay, tank. Come here, tank. Come here.
盖里 怎么样了 还好吗
Gary, are you okay? Are you okay?
跟我说说
Talk to me.
这都是什么
What are those things?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
嘘
Shh.
嘘！
Shh!
哦 糟糕 蹲下
Oh, shit! Get down.
蹲下 蹲下
Get down. Get down.
哦 老天啊 警察在这
Oh, thank fuck! The cops are here.
- 快 快！  - 妈的！
- Go, go!    - Shit!
我们在这 我们在这
We're over here! We're over here!
我们在这
We're over here!
他们到底去哪了？
Where the fuck did they go?
我们要怎么做
What do we do?
- 不！等下！  - 怎么了？
- No! Wait! - What the fuck?
坦克 坦克
Tank, tank.
嘿 伙计 你还好吗 怎么样了？
Buddy, are you okay? Are you okay?
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay, buddy.
兰迪！  兰迪！
Randy! Randy!
兰迪 求你了！  盖里 离近点…
Randy, please! Gary, stay close to...
跑！  跑！
Run! Run!
跑啊  盖里！
Run, Gary!
加油 盖里！快点跑！
Come on, Gary. Hurry! Run!
进去 进去 进去 进去
Get in. Get in. Get in. Get in.
盖里 你怎么样？  还好吗
You okay, Gary? Are you okay?
- 我很害怕  - 我知道
- I'm scared. - I know.
都会好的
It's gonna be okay.
上楼梯
Get up the ladder.
在这  我会给你坦克 上楼梯
Here, I'll give you tank. Get up the ladder.
带上他 快点 坦克
Take him. Come on, tank.
啊  盖里！  哦  天哪
Aah, Gary! Oh, my God!
詹妮
Jenn!
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
坦克 别赶我走！
Tank, don't let go of me!
换句话说 我准备好了
In other words, I think I'm ready.
我知道很多关于你知道我妈妈的事
I know a lot of you know my mother,
而我只是想让你们明白
and I just wanted to make sure that you guys know
她支持我的决定
that she supports my decision.
好了 现在是时候为我…
Okay, now, it's time for me...
为我自己做盘磁带了
To make a tape for myself.
谢谢你来看我
Thanks for watching.
宝贝？
Baby?